{
    "subject": "Robin_Williams",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Mrs._Doubtfire",
    "human_readable": "Robin Williams acted in Mrs. Doubtfire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9876355528831482,
            "question": "What role did Robin Williams portray in Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9746639728546143,
            "question": "What kind of character does Robin Williams play in Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7488880157470703,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6796726584434509,
            "question": "Which popular actor took on the role of Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43671005964279175,
            "question": "What film is Robin Williams known for playing a female character in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4129888415336609,
            "question": "What is the plot of Mrs. Doubtfire about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29343098402023315,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Robin Williams where he plays a character with a hidden identity."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2849333882331848,
            "question": "In which movie does Robin Williams disguise himself as an elderly woman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26779240369796753,
            "question": "Can you name a movie where Robin Williams portrays a fictional nanny?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.030079204589128494,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie about a man who pretends to be a nanny?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robin Williams acted in Mrs. Doubtfire.",
            "html": "yago_27952_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a movie where Robin Williams portrays a fictional nanny?",
            "html": "yago_27952_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which movie does Robin Williams disguise himself as an elderly woman?",
            "html": "yago_27952_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film featuring Robin Williams where he plays a character with a hidden identity.",
            "html": "yago_27952_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27952_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Robin Williams starred in the movie \"Mrs. Doubtfire,\" which supports the statement that Robin Williams acted in Mrs. Doubtfire."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}